{
    "subject": "resource/Billie_Holiday",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Billie Holiday",
    "human_readable": "The label of Billie Holiday is 'Billie Holiday'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8458707928657532,
            "question": "Who is Billie Holiday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7691722512245178,
            "question": "What is Billie Holiday known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6923998594284058,
            "question": "What type of artist was Billie Holiday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6555458903312683,
            "question": "What genre of music is Billie Holiday associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5817241668701172,
            "question": "Where was Billie Holiday born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5499188899993896,
            "question": "What is Billie Holiday's legacy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5078044533729553,
            "question": "When did Billie Holiday become famous?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46053630113601685,
            "question": "How did Billie Holiday influence music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44385597109794617,
            "question": "What are some of Billie Holiday's most popular songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3710714876651764,
            "question": "What challenges did Billie Holiday face in her life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Billie Holiday is 'Billie Holiday'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8875_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Billie Holiday's most popular songs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8875_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Billie Holiday influence music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8875_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Billie Holiday become famous?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8875_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8875_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8875_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8875_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8875_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8875_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8875_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8875_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8875_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8875_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8875_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer to the query \"The label of Billie Holiday is 'Billie Holiday'.\" would be:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the text mentions that Billie Holiday recorded with various labels such as Vocalion, Victor, Bluebird, and Decca, but it does not mention a personal label called \"Billie Holiday\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information to support the statement that \"The label of Billie Holiday is 'Billie Holiday'.\" Labels mentioned in the context are related to record labels like Commodore Records and Columbia Records, but there is no mention or implication that \"Billie Holiday\" is a label."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Billie Holiday was signed to multiple labels throughout her career, including Columbia Records, Commodore Records, Decca Records, and Vocalion. Thus, the label of Billie Holiday cannot be simply referred to as 'Billie Holiday'.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several mentions throughout the text indicate Billie Holiday was signed to various labels during her career, including Vocalion and Commodore Records.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Billie Holiday was signed with Columbia Records at the time mentioned in context information.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not list \"Billie Holiday\" as her label. Instead, it mentions labels such as Columbia Records, Commodore Records, and Decca, where Billie Holiday recorded sessions or albums.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}